Hello. My name is Paul Cheney, and
welcome to my course on Hands-on Response
and Design Using a CSS Preprocessor.
I teach digital media at UVU, and in my
spare time I build courses for
Pluralsight.
A CSS preprocessor allows you to use many
programming functions to build your CSS
that you may never have thought possible.
In this course, we will show you how you
create many separate files for your CSS,
and then automatically
combine and minify them for delivery to
the web. We will also show you the power
of using variables,
nesting your CSS, and how to use mix ins
to automate code creation.
We will also leverage the power of
inheritance to create dry code, as well
as explore math functions, and control
directives.
This is hands-on course, so you'll be
working right
alongside me to build a responsive,
mobile-first website for Aspen Dental.
Even if you don't like the dentist,
you're going to love the final product.
Before beginning the course you should be
familiar with HTML5, CSS3, and media
queries.
I hope you'll join me, and give me a
chance to convince you that using a CSS
preprocessor is the way to go.